A Guide to the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginai, Special Commmittee on the Nomination of Chancellor Clinch Valley College, 1984, 1993
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Board of Visitors, Special Commmittee on the Nomination of Chancellor Clinch Valley College 1984, 1993
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/1/3.971
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Closed until 2090. Access before then requires written permission from the Office of the Legal Advisor.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1997 March 12.
Contents List
- Advertisements, Re: Search 1993 (Box 1)
- Briefing Book, CLinch Valley College (John T. Casteen) 1993 (Box 1)
- Candidates (1-184), List of Clinch Valley College--Chancellor Search 1993 (Box 1)
- Candidates (A-Z), List of Clinch Valley College--Chancellor Search 1993 (Box 1)
- Candidates, Short List 1993 (Box 1)
- Candidate #1 - Candidate #17, Clinch Valley College (17 folders) 1993 (Box 1)
- Candidate #18 - Candidate #52, Clinch Valley College (35 folders) 1993 (Box 2)
- Candidate #53 - Candidate #92, Clinch Valley College (40 folders) 1993 (Box 3)
- Candidate #93 - Candidate #138, Clinch Valley College (46 folders) 1993 (Box 4)
- Candidate #139 - Candidate #174, Clinch Valley College (35 folders) 1993 (Box 5)
- Candidate #175 - Candidate #184, Clinch Valley College (10 folders) 1993 (Box 6)
- Clinch Valley College 1993 (Box 6)
- Executive Committee Members 1993 (Box 6)
- Expenses, Re: Search Committee 1993 (Box 6)
- Finalists for Chancellor Search 1993 (Box 6)
- Meetings of the Search Committee 1993 (Box 6)
- Members of the Search Committee 1993 (Box 6)
- Minutes of the Search Committee Meeting 1993 (Box 6)
- Nomination of a Chancellor, Special Committee of the Board of Visitors 1984 (Box 6)
- Rating and Resume Sheet 1993 (Box 6)
- Search Committee-Clinch Valley College 1993 (Box 6)